Guide to the Bingham Oceanographic Laboratory, Peabody Museum of Natural History, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Correspondence, 1927-1964; Series I
  - 1960
    - Woods Hole Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 35, Folder 504)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 35, Folder 505)
    - W (Box 35, Folder 506)
    - Y (Box 35, Folder 507)
    - Zoology 113 (Box 35, Folder 508)
    - Zoology - Doctoral dissertations (Box 35, Folder 508a)
  - 1961
    - A (Box 35, Folder 509)
    - Applications - students (Box 35, Folder 510)
    - Bermuda Biological Station (Box 35, Folder 511)
    - Bingham Laboratory Advisory Committee (Box 35, Folder 512)
    - Book List (Box 35, Folder 513)
    - B (Box 35, Folder 514)
    - C (Box 35, Folder 515)
    - D (Box 35, Folder 516)
    - E (Box 35, Folder 517)
    - F (Box 35, Folder 518)
    - G (Box 35, Folder 519)
    - Graduate School (Box 35, Folder 520)
    - H (Box 35, Folder 521)
    - I (Box 35, Folder 522)
    - J (Box 35, Folder 523)
    - K (Box 35, Folder 524)
    - L (Box 35, Folder 525)
    - Mc (Box 36, Folder 526)
    - M (Box 36, Folder 527)
    - Marine Biology of India (Box 36, Folder 528)
    - NSF - proposals reviewed (Box 36, Folder 529)
    - NSF - Committee on Research and Education (Box 36, Folder 530)
    - New York Zoological Society (Box 36, Folder 531)
    - Oceanography Department (Box 36, Folder 532)
    - O (Box 36, Folder 533)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 36, Folder 534)
    - Pergamon Press (Box 36, Folder 535)
    - P (Box 36, Folder 536)
    - R (Box 36, Folder 537)
    - Recommendations (Box 36, Folder 538)
    - Requests for information (Box 36, Folder 539)
    - Shallow Water Research (Box 36, Folder 540)
    - Ships and Salvage (Box 36, Folder 541)
    - S (Box 36, Folder 542)
    - T (Box 36, Folder 543)
    - U (Box 36, Folder 544)
    - V (Box 36, Folder 545)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 36, Folder 546-547)
    - Woods Hole Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 37, Folder 548)
    - W (Box 37, Folder 549)
    - Y (Box 37, Folder 550)
    - Zoology Department (Box 37, Folder 551)
  - 1962
    - American Society of Limnology and Oceanography (Box 37, Folder 552)
    - Atlantic Shelf Studies (Box 37, Folder 553)
    - Applications - Students (Box 37, Folder 554)
    - A (Box 37, Folder 555)
    - Bermuda Biological Station (Box 37, Folder 556)
    - Bingham Advisory Committee (Box 37, Folder 557)
    - Biology Department (Box 37, Folder 558)
    - Boyd, William A., Jr. (Box 37, Folder 559)
    - B (Box 37, Folder 560)
    - C (Box 37, Folder 561)
    - D (Box 37, Folder 562)
    - F (Box 37, Folder 563)
    - Geology 195b (Box 37, Folder 564)
    - G (Box 37, Folder 565)
    - H (Box 37, Folder 566)
    - J (Box 37, Folder 567)
    - K (Box 37, Folder 568)
    - L (Box 37, Folder 569)
    - Lectures (Box 37, Folder 570)
    - M (Box 37, Folder 571)
    - National Oceanographic Data Center (Box 37, Folder 572)
    - NSF - Marine Conference (Box 37, Folder 573)
    - NSF - proposals (Box 37, Folder 574)
    - New York Zoological Society (Box 37, Folder 575)
    - Observational Oceanography (Box 37, Folder 576)
    - Oceanography Department (Box 37, Folder 577)
    - O (Box 37, Folder 578)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 37, Folder 579)
    - P (Box 37, Folder 580)
    - Panoramic Studios - Maps (Box 38, Folder 581)
    - President's Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 38, Folder 582)
    - Requests for Information (Box 38, Folder 583)
    - Recommendations (Box 38, Folder 584)
    - R (Box 38, Folder 585)
    - Ships and Salvage (Box 38, Folder 586)
    - S (Box 38, Folder 587)
    - T (Box 38, Folder 588)
    - V (Box 38, Folder 589)
    - Woods Hole Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 38, Folder 590)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 38, Folder 591-592)
    - W (Box 38, Folder 593)
    - Zoology Department (Box 38, Folder 594)
    - X-Y-Z (Box 38, Folder 595)
  - 1963
    - American Society of Limnology and Oceanography (Box 38, Folder 596)
    - Applications - students (Box 38, Folder 597)
    - Atlantic Shelf Studies (Box 38, Folder 598)
    - A (Box 38, Folder 599)
    - Bermuda Biological Station (Box 38, Folder 600)
    - Bingham Advisory Committee (Box 39, Folder 601)
    - Biology Department (Box 39, Folder 602)
    - Bulletin - Bingham Oceanographic Collection (Box 39, Folder 603)
    - Bulletin - Bingham Oceanographic Collection Editorial Board (Box 39, Folder 604)
    - B (Box 39, Folder 605)
    - CCTA/CSA (Box 39, Folder 606)
    - C (Box 39, Folder 607)
    - D (Box 39, Folder 608)
    - F (Box 39, Folder 609)
    - H (Box 39, Folder 610)
    - K (Box 39, Folder 611)
    - M (Box 39, Folder 612)
    - NAS/NSF Committee on Oceanography (Box 39, Folder 613)
    - National Oceanographic Data Center (Box 39, Folder 614)
    - NSF proposals (Box 39, Folder 615)
    - New York Zoological Society (Box 39, Folder 616)
    - Oceanography Department (Box 39, Folder 617)
    - Office of Science and Technology (Box 39, Folder 618)
    - O (Box 39, Folder 619)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 39, Folder 620)
    - P (Box 39, Folder 621)
    - Recommendations (Box 39, Folder 622)
    - Requests for information (Box 39, Folder 623)
    - R (Box 39, Folder 624)
    - S (Box 39, Folder 625)
    - T (Box 39, Folder 626)
    - U (Box 39, Folder 627)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 39, Folder 628-629)
    - Woods Hole Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 40, Folder 630)
  - 1964
    - American Society of Limnology and Oceanography (Box 40, Folder 631)
    - Applications - students (Box 40, Folder 632)
    - Atlantic Shelf Studies (Box 40, Folder 633)
    - A (Box 40, Folder 634)
    - Bermuda Biological Station (Box 40, Folder 635)
    - Biology Department (Box 40, Folder 636)
    - Biology 562 (Box 40, Folder 637)
    - Bingham Advisory Committee (Box 40, Folder 638)
    - Bulletin - Bingham Oceanographic Collection (Box 40, Folder 639)
    - B (Box 40, Folder 640)
    - C (Box 40, Folder 641)
    - D (Box 40, Folder 642)
    - E (Box 40, Folder 643)
    - F (Box 40, Folder 644)
    - G (Box 40, Folder 645)
    - H (Box 40, Folder 646)
    - I (Box 40, Folder 647)
    - K (Box 40, Folder 648)
    - Link Foundation Fellowships (Box 40, Folder 649)
    - L (Box 40, Folder 650)
    - Mc (Box 40, Folder 651)
    - Mystic River Estuary (Box 40, Folder 652)
    - M (Box 40, Folder 653)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Oceanography (Box 40, Folder 654)
    - NSF proposals (Box 40, Folder 655)
    - National Oceanographic Data Center (Box 40, Folder 656)
    - New York Zoological Society (Box 40, Folder 657)
    - N (Box 40, Folder 658)
    - Oceanography Department (Box 41, Folder 659)
    - Office of Science and Technology (Box 41, Folder 660)
    - O (Box 41, Folder 661)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 41, Folder 662)
    - P (Box 41, Folder 663)
    - Recommendations (Box 41, Folder 664)
    - Requests for information (Box 41, Folder 665)
    - R (Box 41, Folder 666)
    - S (Box 41, Folder 667)
    - T (Box 41, Folder 668)
    - UNESCO Inter-government Oceanographic Committee (Box 41, Folder 669)
    - United Aircraft Products (Box 41, Folder 670)
    - V (Box 41, Folder 671)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 41, Folder 672)
    - W (Box 41, Folder 673)
    - X-Y-Z (Box 41, Folder 674)
- Subject Files, 1931-1965; Series II
  Office records are arranged by subseries and then chronologically. Personnel records are arranged by subseries and then chronologically. Miscellaneous is arranged alphabetically.
  - Office Records
    - Peabody Museum Report, 1959-1960, 1962-1965 (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
    - President's Reports, 1931-1932, 1959-1965 (Box 42, Folder 5-11)
    - Research Grant List, 1960-1965 (Box 42, Folder 12-16)
  - Personnel Records
    - Staff Activities, 1957-1965 (Box 42, Folder 17-25)
    - Staff Appointments, 1958-1965 (Box 42, Folder 26-31)
    - Staff Publications, 1959-1965 (Box 42, Folder 32-37)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Expedition Equipment, 1932-1934 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Laboratory Materials, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 39)